[{"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "a.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "b.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "c.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "d.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "e.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "f.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "g.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "h.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "i.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "j.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "k.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "l.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "m.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": ["v.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk."], "flags": 33792, "question": "hk.", "authority": [], "server": "c.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": ["v.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk."], "flags": 33792, "question": "hk.", "authority": [], "server": "x.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": ["d.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk."], "flags": 33792, "question": "hk.", "authority": [], "server": "v.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": ["d.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk."], "flags": 33792, "question": "hk.", "authority": [], "server": "y.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": ["u.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk."], "flags": 33792, "question": "hk.", "authority": [], "server": "d.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": ["u.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk."], "flags": 33792, "question": "hk.", "authority": [], "server": "z.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": ["d.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk."], "flags": 33792, "question": "hk.", "authority": [], "server": "w.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": ["w.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk."], "flags": 33792, "question": "hk.", "authority": [], "server": "u.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "a.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "b.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "c.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "d.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "e.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "f.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "g.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "h.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "i.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "j.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "k.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "l.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "m.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk.", "hk-ns.pch.net.", "ns8.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "c.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk.", "hk-ns.pch.net.", "ns8.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "y.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "ns8.hkirc.net.hk.", "hk-ns.pch.net.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "u.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk.", "hk-ns.pch.net.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "ns8.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "w.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "ns8.hkirc.net.hk.", "hk-ns.pch.net.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "d.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "v.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "z.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "ns8.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk.", "hk-ns.pch.net."], "server": "x.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "ns7.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "hk-ns.pch.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "ns8.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "a.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "b.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "c.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "d.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "e.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "f.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "g.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "h.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "i.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "j.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "k.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "l.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "m.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "hk-ns.pch.net.", "ns8.hkirc.net.hk.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "y.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "z.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "v.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk.", "ns8.hkirc.net.hk.", "hk-ns.pch.net.", "z.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "w.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "ns8.hkirc.net.hk.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk.", "hk-ns.pch.net.", "z.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "d.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk.", "ns8.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "hk-ns.pch.net."], "server": "x.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "ns8.hkirc.net.hk.", "hk-ns.pch.net.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "u.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "ns8.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk.", "hk-ns.pch.net."], "server": "c.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "hk-ns.pch.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "ns8.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "ns7.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "a.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "b.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "c.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "d.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "e.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "f.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "g.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "h.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "i.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "j.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "k.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "l.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "m.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "ns8.hkirc.net.hk.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "hk-ns.pch.net."], "server": "w.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "ns8.hkirc.net.hk.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk.", "hk-ns.pch.net."], "server": "x.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "ns8.hkirc.net.hk.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "hk-ns.pch.net."], "server": "y.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "ns8.hkirc.net.hk.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk.", "hk-ns.pch.net.", "z.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "c.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk.", "hk-ns.pch.net.", "ns8.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "u.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk.", "ns8.hkirc.net.hk.", "hk-ns.pch.net."], "server": "d.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "v.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "z.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "ns8.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "ns7.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "hk-ns.pch.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "a.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "b.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "c.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "d.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "e.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "f.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "g.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "h.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "i.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "j.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "k.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "l.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "m.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "z.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk.", "ns8.hkirc.net.hk.", "hk-ns.pch.net.", "z.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "u.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk.", "hk-ns.pch.net.", "ns8.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "x.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk.", "hk-ns.pch.net.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "ns8.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "d.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "v.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "hk-ns.pch.net.", "ns8.hkirc.net.hk.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "y.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk.", "hk-ns.pch.net.", "ns8.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "w.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "hk-ns.pch.net.", "ns8.hkirc.net.hk.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "c.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "ns7.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "ns8.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "hk-ns.pch.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "a.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "b.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "c.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "d.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "e.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "f.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "g.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "h.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "i.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "j.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "k.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "l.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "m.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "v.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "ns8.hkirc.net.hk.", "hk-ns.pch.net.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "w.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "ns8.hkirc.net.hk.", "hk-ns.pch.net.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "d.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "z.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "ns8.hkirc.net.hk.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk.", "hk-ns.pch.net."], "server": "x.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "hk-ns.pch.net.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk.", "ns8.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "c.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "ns8.hkirc.net.hk.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "hk-ns.pch.net."], "server": "y.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "hk-ns.pch.net.", "ns8.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "u.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "ns7.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "ns8.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "hk-ns.pch.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "a.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "b.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "c.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "d.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "e.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "f.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "g.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "h.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "i.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "j.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "k.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "l.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "m.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "hk-ns.pch.net.", "ns8.hkirc.net.hk.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "w.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "z.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk.", "ns8.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "hk-ns.pch.net."], "server": "u.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "ns8.hkirc.net.hk.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "hk-ns.pch.net."], "server": "d.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "ns8.hkirc.net.hk.", "hk-ns.pch.net.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "x.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "v.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "hk-ns.pch.net.", "ns8.hkirc.net.hk.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "y.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk.", "ns8.hkirc.net.hk.", "hk-ns.pch.net.", "z.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "c.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "hk-ns.pch.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "ns8.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "ns7.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "a.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "b.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "c.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "d.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "e.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "f.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "g.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "h.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "i.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "j.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "k.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "l.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "m.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "ns8.hkirc.net.hk.", "hk-ns.pch.net."], "server": "u.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "v.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "ns8.hkirc.net.hk.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk.", "hk-ns.pch.net.", "z.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "x.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk.", "hk-ns.pch.net.", "ns8.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "w.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "z.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "ns8.hkirc.net.hk.", "hk-ns.pch.net.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "y.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk.", "hk-ns.pch.net.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "ns8.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "d.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "hk-ns.pch.net.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk.", "ns8.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "c.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "ns7.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "ns8.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "hk-ns.pch.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "a.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "b.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "c.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "d.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "e.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "f.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "g.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "h.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "i.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "j.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "k.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "l.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "m.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "hk-ns.pch.net.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "ns8.hkirc.net.hk.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "c.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "z.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "ns8.hkirc.net.hk.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk.", "hk-ns.pch.net."], "server": "d.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "hk-ns.pch.net.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "ns8.hkirc.net.hk.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "x.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "hk-ns.pch.net.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk.", "ns8.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "y.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "hk-ns.pch.net.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "ns8.hkirc.net.hk.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "u.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "v.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "hk-ns.pch.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "ns8.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "ns7.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "ns7.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "a.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "ns7.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "b.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "ns7.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "c.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "ns7.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "d.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "ns7.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "e.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "ns7.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "f.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "ns7.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "g.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "ns7.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "h.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "ns7.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "i.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "ns7.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "j.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "ns7.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "k.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "ns7.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "l.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "ns7.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "m.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "ns7.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "z.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "ns7.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk.", "hk-ns.pch.net.", "ns8.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "x.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "ns7.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "ns8.hkirc.net.hk.", "hk-ns.pch.net."], "server": "u.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "ns7.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "ns8.hkirc.net.hk.", "hk-ns.pch.net.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "d.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "ns7.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "hk-ns.pch.net.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk.", "ns8.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "c.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "ns7.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "hk-ns.pch.net.", "ns8.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "w.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "ns7.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "hk-ns.pch.net.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "ns8.hkirc.net.hk.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "y.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "ns7.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "v.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "ns7.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "ns7.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "ns7.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "hk-ns.pch.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "ns7.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "ns8.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "hk-ns.pch.net.", "authority": ["net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "a.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "hk-ns.pch.net.", "authority": ["net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "b.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "hk-ns.pch.net.", "authority": ["net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "c.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "hk-ns.pch.net.", "authority": ["net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "d.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "hk-ns.pch.net.", "authority": ["net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "e.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "hk-ns.pch.net.", "authority": ["net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "f.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "hk-ns.pch.net.", "authority": ["net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "g.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "hk-ns.pch.net.", "authority": ["net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "h.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "hk-ns.pch.net.", "authority": ["net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "i.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "hk-ns.pch.net.", "authority": ["net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "j.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "hk-ns.pch.net.", "authority": ["net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "k.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "hk-ns.pch.net.", "authority": ["net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "l.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "hk-ns.pch.net.", "authority": ["net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "m.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "hk-ns.pch.net.", "authority": ["pch.net.", "ns2.pch.net.", "anyns.pch.net.", "ns3.pch.net."], "server": "j.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "hk-ns.pch.net.", "authority": ["pch.net.", "ns2.pch.net.", "anyns.pch.net.", "ns3.pch.net."], "server": "g.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "hk-ns.pch.net.", "authority": ["pch.net.", "ns2.pch.net.", "anyns.pch.net.", "ns3.pch.net."], "server": "i.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "hk-ns.pch.net.", "authority": ["pch.net.", "ns2.pch.net.", "anyns.pch.net.", "ns3.pch.net."], "server": "f.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "hk-ns.pch.net.", "authority": ["pch.net.", "ns2.pch.net.", "anyns.pch.net.", "ns3.pch.net."], "server": "m.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "hk-ns.pch.net.", "authority": ["pch.net.", "ns2.pch.net.", "anyns.pch.net.", "ns3.pch.net."], "server": "d.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "hk-ns.pch.net.", "authority": ["pch.net.", "ns2.pch.net.", "anyns.pch.net.", "ns3.pch.net."], "server": "c.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "hk-ns.pch.net.", "authority": ["pch.net.", "ns2.pch.net.", "anyns.pch.net.", "ns3.pch.net."], "server": "a.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "hk-ns.pch.net.", "authority": ["pch.net.", "ns2.pch.net.", "anyns.pch.net.", "ns3.pch.net."], "server": "h.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "hk-ns.pch.net.", "authority": ["pch.net.", "ns2.pch.net.", "anyns.pch.net.", "ns3.pch.net."], "server": "l.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "hk-ns.pch.net.", "authority": ["pch.net.", "ns2.pch.net.", "anyns.pch.net.", "ns3.pch.net."], "server": "e.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "hk-ns.pch.net.", "authority": ["pch.net.", "ns2.pch.net.", "anyns.pch.net.", "ns3.pch.net."], "server": "k.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "hk-ns.pch.net.", "authority": ["pch.net.", "ns2.pch.net.", "anyns.pch.net.", "ns3.pch.net."], "server": "b.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "hk-ns.pch.net.", "authority": ["pch.net.", "anyns.pch.net."], "server": "ns2.pch.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "hk-ns.pch.net.", "authority": ["pch.net.", "anyns.pch.net."], "server": "anyns.pch.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "hk-ns.pch.net.", "authority": ["pch.net.", "anyns.pch.net."], "server": "ns3.pch.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "ns8.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "a.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "ns8.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "b.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "ns8.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "c.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "ns8.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "d.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "ns8.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "e.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "ns8.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "f.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "ns8.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "g.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "ns8.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "h.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "ns8.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "i.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "ns8.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "j.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "ns8.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "k.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "ns8.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "l.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "ns8.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hk.", "y.hkirc.net.hk.", "u.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "v.hkirc.net.hk.", "w.hkirc.net.hk.", "x.hkirc.net.hk.", "c.hkirc.net.hk.", "d.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "m.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "ns8.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "ns8.hkirc.net.hk.", "hk-ns.pch.net.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "d.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "ns8.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "hk-ns.pch.net.", "ns8.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "y.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "ns8.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk.", "ns8.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "hk-ns.pch.net."], "server": "w.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "ns8.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk.", "hk-ns.pch.net.", "ns8.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "x.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "ns8.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "z.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "ns8.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "v.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "ns8.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "hk-ns.pch.net.", "ns8.hkirc.net.hk.", "z.hkirc.net.hk.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "c.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "ns8.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "ns8.hkirc.net.hk.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk.", "hk-ns.pch.net.", "z.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "u.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "ns8.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "ns8.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "ns8.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "hk-ns.pch.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "ns8.hkirc.net.hk.", "authority": ["hkirc.net.hk.", "ns7.hkirc.net.hk."], "server": "ns7.hkirc.net.hk."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "j.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "a.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "j.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "b.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "j.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "c.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "j.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "d.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "j.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "e.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "j.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "f.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "j.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "g.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "j.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "h.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "j.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "i.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "j.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "j.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "j.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "k.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "j.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "l.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "j.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "m.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "j.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "k.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "j.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "i.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "j.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "l.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "j.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "a.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "j.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "b.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "j.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "f.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "j.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "e.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "j.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "g.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "j.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "c.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "j.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "m.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "j.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "d.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "j.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "j.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "j.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "h.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "j.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "av1.nstld.com."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "j.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "av2.nstld.com."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "j.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "av3.nstld.com."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "j.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "av4.nstld.com."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "g.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "a.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "g.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "b.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "g.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "c.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "g.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "d.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "g.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "e.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "g.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "f.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "g.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "g.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "g.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "h.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "g.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "i.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "g.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "j.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "g.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "k.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "g.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "l.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "g.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "m.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "g.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "l.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "g.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "a.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "g.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "h.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "g.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "m.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "g.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "d.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "g.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "b.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "g.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "g.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "g.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "c.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "g.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "j.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "g.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "e.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "g.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "f.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "g.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "k.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "g.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "i.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "g.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "av1.nstld.com."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "g.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "av2.nstld.com."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "g.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "av3.nstld.com."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "g.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "av4.nstld.com."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "i.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "a.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "i.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "b.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "i.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "c.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "i.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "d.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "i.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "e.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "i.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "f.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "i.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "g.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "i.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "h.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "i.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "i.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "i.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "j.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "i.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "k.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "i.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "l.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "i.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "m.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "i.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "d.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "i.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "h.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "i.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "e.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "i.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "i.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "i.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "j.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "i.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "b.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "i.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "m.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "i.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "f.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "i.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "c.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "i.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "k.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "i.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "g.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "i.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "l.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "i.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "a.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "i.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "av1.nstld.com."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "i.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "av2.nstld.com."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "i.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "av3.nstld.com."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "i.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "av4.nstld.com."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "f.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "a.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "f.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "b.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "f.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "c.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "f.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "d.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "f.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "e.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "f.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "f.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "f.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "g.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "f.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "h.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "f.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "i.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "f.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "j.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "f.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "k.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "f.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "l.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "f.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "m.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "f.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "h.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "f.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "l.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "f.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "e.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "f.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "g.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "f.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "c.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "f.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "m.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "f.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "f.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "f.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "b.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "f.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "d.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "f.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "j.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "f.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "a.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "f.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "k.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "f.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "i.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "f.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "av1.nstld.com."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "f.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "av2.nstld.com."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "f.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "av3.nstld.com."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "f.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "av4.nstld.com."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "m.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "a.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "m.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "b.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "m.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "c.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "m.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "d.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "m.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "e.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "m.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "f.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "m.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "g.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "m.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "h.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "m.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "i.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "m.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "j.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "m.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "k.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "m.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "l.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "m.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "m.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "m.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "j.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "m.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "f.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "m.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "g.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "m.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "i.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "m.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "a.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "m.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "k.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "m.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "m.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "m.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "h.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "m.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "c.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "m.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "e.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "m.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "l.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "m.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "d.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "m.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "b.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "m.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "av1.nstld.com."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "m.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "av2.nstld.com."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "m.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "av3.nstld.com."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "m.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "av4.nstld.com."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "a.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "b.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "c.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "d.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "e.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "f.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "g.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "h.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "i.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "j.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "k.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "l.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "m.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "f.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "m.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "e.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "j.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "l.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "h.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "d.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "b.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "i.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "g.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "k.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "a.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "c.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "d.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "av1.nstld.com."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "d.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "av2.nstld.com."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "d.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "av3.nstld.com."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "d.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "av4.nstld.com."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "a.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "b.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "c.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "d.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "e.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "f.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "g.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "h.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "i.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "j.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "k.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "l.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "m.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "l.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "m.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "c.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "k.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "j.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "b.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "e.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "d.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "h.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "g.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "i.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "a.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "f.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "c.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "av1.nstld.com."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "c.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "av2.nstld.com."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "c.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "av3.nstld.com."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "c.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "av4.nstld.com."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "a.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "b.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "c.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "d.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "e.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "f.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "g.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "h.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "i.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "j.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "k.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "l.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "m.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "g.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "m.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "b.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "a.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "f.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "c.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "l.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "j.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "k.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "i.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "d.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "h.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "e.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "a.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "av1.nstld.com."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "a.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "av2.nstld.com."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "a.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "av3.nstld.com."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "a.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "av4.nstld.com."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "h.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "a.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "h.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "b.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "h.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "c.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "h.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "d.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "h.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "e.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "h.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "f.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "h.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "g.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "h.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "h.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "h.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "i.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "h.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "j.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "h.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "k.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "h.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "l.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "h.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "m.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "h.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "m.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "h.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "j.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "h.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "i.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "h.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "d.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "h.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "a.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "h.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "e.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "h.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "c.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "h.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "k.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "h.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "b.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "h.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "g.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "h.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "f.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "h.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "h.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "h.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "l.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "h.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "av1.nstld.com."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "h.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "av2.nstld.com."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "h.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "av3.nstld.com."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "h.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "av4.nstld.com."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "l.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "a.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "l.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "b.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "l.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "c.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "l.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "d.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "l.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "e.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "l.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "f.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "l.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "g.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "l.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "h.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "l.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "i.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "l.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "j.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "l.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "k.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "l.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "l.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "l.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "m.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "l.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "e.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "l.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "j.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "l.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "c.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "l.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "b.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "l.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "d.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "l.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "g.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "l.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "h.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "l.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "m.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "l.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "l.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "l.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "a.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "l.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "i.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "l.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "k.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "l.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "f.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "l.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "av1.nstld.com."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "l.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "av2.nstld.com."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "l.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "av3.nstld.com."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "l.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "av4.nstld.com."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "e.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "a.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "e.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "b.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "e.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "c.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "e.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "d.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "e.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "e.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "e.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "f.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "e.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "g.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "e.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "h.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "e.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "i.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "e.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "j.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "e.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "k.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "e.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "l.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "e.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "m.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "e.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "b.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "e.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "c.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "e.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "m.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "e.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "j.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "e.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "i.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "e.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "a.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "e.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "h.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "e.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "f.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "e.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "l.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "e.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "g.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "e.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "e.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "e.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "k.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "e.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "d.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "e.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "av1.nstld.com."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "e.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "av2.nstld.com."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "e.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "av3.nstld.com."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "e.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "av4.nstld.com."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "k.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "a.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "k.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "b.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "k.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "c.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "k.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "d.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "k.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "e.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "k.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "f.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "k.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "g.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "k.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "h.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "k.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "i.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "k.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "j.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "k.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "k.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "k.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "l.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "k.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "m.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "k.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "c.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "k.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "f.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "k.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "i.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "k.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "e.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "k.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "m.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "k.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "h.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "k.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "d.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "k.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "b.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "k.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "l.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "k.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "a.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "k.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "g.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "k.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "k.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "k.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "j.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "k.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "av1.nstld.com."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "k.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "av2.nstld.com."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "k.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "av3.nstld.com."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "k.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "av4.nstld.com."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "a.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "b.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "c.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "d.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "e.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "f.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "g.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "h.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "i.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "j.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "k.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "l.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "m.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "h.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "f.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "l.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "b.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "m.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "j.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "c.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "g.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "e.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "i.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "a.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "k.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "d.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "b.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "av1.nstld.com."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "b.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "av2.nstld.com."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "b.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "av3.nstld.com."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "b.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["gtld-servers.net.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "av4.nstld.com."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "ns2.pch.net.", "authority": ["net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "a.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "ns2.pch.net.", "authority": ["net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "b.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "ns2.pch.net.", "authority": ["net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "c.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "ns2.pch.net.", "authority": ["net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "d.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "ns2.pch.net.", "authority": ["net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "e.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "ns2.pch.net.", "authority": ["net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "f.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "ns2.pch.net.", "authority": ["net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "g.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "ns2.pch.net.", "authority": ["net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "h.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "ns2.pch.net.", "authority": ["net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "i.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "ns2.pch.net.", "authority": ["net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "j.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "ns2.pch.net.", "authority": ["net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "k.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "ns2.pch.net.", "authority": ["net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "l.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "ns2.pch.net.", "authority": ["net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "m.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "ns2.pch.net.", "authority": ["pch.net.", "ns2.pch.net.", "anyns.pch.net.", "ns3.pch.net."], "server": "m.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "ns2.pch.net.", "authority": ["pch.net.", "ns2.pch.net.", "anyns.pch.net.", "ns3.pch.net."], "server": "j.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "ns2.pch.net.", "authority": ["pch.net.", "ns2.pch.net.", "anyns.pch.net.", "ns3.pch.net."], "server": "d.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "ns2.pch.net.", "authority": ["pch.net.", "ns2.pch.net.", "anyns.pch.net.", "ns3.pch.net."], "server": "f.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "ns2.pch.net.", "authority": ["pch.net.", "ns2.pch.net.", "anyns.pch.net.", "ns3.pch.net."], "server": "i.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "ns2.pch.net.", "authority": ["pch.net.", "ns2.pch.net.", "anyns.pch.net.", "ns3.pch.net."], "server": "g.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "ns2.pch.net.", "authority": ["pch.net.", "ns2.pch.net.", "anyns.pch.net.", "ns3.pch.net."], "server": "l.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "ns2.pch.net.", "authority": ["pch.net.", "ns2.pch.net.", "anyns.pch.net.", "ns3.pch.net."], "server": "h.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "ns2.pch.net.", "authority": ["pch.net.", "ns2.pch.net.", "anyns.pch.net.", "ns3.pch.net."], "server": "a.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "ns2.pch.net.", "authority": ["pch.net.", "ns2.pch.net.", "anyns.pch.net.", "ns3.pch.net."], "server": "k.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "ns2.pch.net.", "authority": ["pch.net.", "ns2.pch.net.", "anyns.pch.net.", "ns3.pch.net."], "server": "e.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "ns2.pch.net.", "authority": ["pch.net.", "ns2.pch.net.", "anyns.pch.net.", "ns3.pch.net."], "server": "c.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "ns2.pch.net.", "authority": ["pch.net.", "ns2.pch.net.", "anyns.pch.net.", "ns3.pch.net."], "server": "b.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "ns2.pch.net.", "authority": ["pch.net.", "anyns.pch.net."], "server": "ns2.pch.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "ns2.pch.net.", "authority": ["pch.net.", "anyns.pch.net."], "server": "anyns.pch.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "ns2.pch.net.", "authority": ["pch.net.", "anyns.pch.net."], "server": "ns3.pch.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "anyns.pch.net.", "authority": ["net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "a.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "anyns.pch.net.", "authority": ["net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "b.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "anyns.pch.net.", "authority": ["net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "c.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "anyns.pch.net.", "authority": ["net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "d.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "anyns.pch.net.", "authority": ["net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "e.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "anyns.pch.net.", "authority": ["net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "f.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "anyns.pch.net.", "authority": ["net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "g.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "anyns.pch.net.", "authority": ["net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "h.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "anyns.pch.net.", "authority": ["net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "i.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "anyns.pch.net.", "authority": ["net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "j.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "anyns.pch.net.", "authority": ["net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "k.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "anyns.pch.net.", "authority": ["net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "l.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "anyns.pch.net.", "authority": ["net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "m.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "anyns.pch.net.", "authority": ["pch.net.", "ns2.pch.net.", "anyns.pch.net.", "ns3.pch.net."], "server": "h.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "anyns.pch.net.", "authority": ["pch.net.", "ns2.pch.net.", "anyns.pch.net.", "ns3.pch.net."], "server": "c.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "anyns.pch.net.", "authority": ["pch.net.", "ns2.pch.net.", "anyns.pch.net.", "ns3.pch.net."], "server": "l.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "anyns.pch.net.", "authority": ["pch.net.", "ns2.pch.net.", "anyns.pch.net.", "ns3.pch.net."], "server": "f.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "anyns.pch.net.", "authority": ["pch.net.", "ns2.pch.net.", "anyns.pch.net.", "ns3.pch.net."], "server": "j.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "anyns.pch.net.", "authority": ["pch.net.", "ns2.pch.net.", "anyns.pch.net.", "ns3.pch.net."], "server": "g.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "anyns.pch.net.", "authority": ["pch.net.", "ns2.pch.net.", "anyns.pch.net.", "ns3.pch.net."], "server": "i.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "anyns.pch.net.", "authority": ["pch.net.", "ns2.pch.net.", "anyns.pch.net.", "ns3.pch.net."], "server": "m.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "anyns.pch.net.", "authority": ["pch.net.", "ns2.pch.net.", "anyns.pch.net.", "ns3.pch.net."], "server": "b.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "anyns.pch.net.", "authority": ["pch.net.", "ns2.pch.net.", "anyns.pch.net.", "ns3.pch.net."], "server": "k.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "anyns.pch.net.", "authority": ["pch.net.", "ns2.pch.net.", "anyns.pch.net.", "ns3.pch.net."], "server": "e.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "anyns.pch.net.", "authority": ["pch.net.", "ns2.pch.net.", "anyns.pch.net.", "ns3.pch.net."], "server": "d.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "anyns.pch.net.", "authority": ["pch.net.", "ns2.pch.net.", "anyns.pch.net.", "ns3.pch.net."], "server": "a.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "anyns.pch.net.", "authority": ["pch.net.", "anyns.pch.net."], "server": "ns2.pch.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "anyns.pch.net.", "authority": ["pch.net.", "anyns.pch.net."], "server": "anyns.pch.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "anyns.pch.net.", "authority": ["pch.net.", "anyns.pch.net."], "server": "ns3.pch.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "ns3.pch.net.", "authority": ["net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "a.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "ns3.pch.net.", "authority": ["net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "b.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "ns3.pch.net.", "authority": ["net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "c.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "ns3.pch.net.", "authority": ["net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "d.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "ns3.pch.net.", "authority": ["net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "e.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "ns3.pch.net.", "authority": ["net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "f.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "ns3.pch.net.", "authority": ["net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "g.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "ns3.pch.net.", "authority": ["net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "h.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "ns3.pch.net.", "authority": ["net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "i.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "ns3.pch.net.", "authority": ["net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "j.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "ns3.pch.net.", "authority": ["net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "k.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "ns3.pch.net.", "authority": ["net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "l.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "ns3.pch.net.", "authority": ["net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "m.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "ns3.pch.net.", "authority": ["pch.net.", "ns2.pch.net.", "anyns.pch.net.", "ns3.pch.net."], "server": "g.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "ns3.pch.net.", "authority": ["pch.net.", "ns2.pch.net.", "anyns.pch.net.", "ns3.pch.net."], "server": "d.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "ns3.pch.net.", "authority": ["pch.net.", "ns2.pch.net.", "anyns.pch.net.", "ns3.pch.net."], "server": "h.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "ns3.pch.net.", "authority": ["pch.net.", "ns2.pch.net.", "anyns.pch.net.", "ns3.pch.net."], "server": "m.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "ns3.pch.net.", "authority": ["pch.net.", "ns2.pch.net.", "anyns.pch.net.", "ns3.pch.net."], "server": "j.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "ns3.pch.net.", "authority": ["pch.net.", "ns2.pch.net.", "anyns.pch.net.", "ns3.pch.net."], "server": "l.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "ns3.pch.net.", "authority": ["pch.net.", "ns2.pch.net.", "anyns.pch.net.", "ns3.pch.net."], "server": "a.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "ns3.pch.net.", "authority": ["pch.net.", "ns2.pch.net.", "anyns.pch.net.", "ns3.pch.net."], "server": "f.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "ns3.pch.net.", "authority": ["pch.net.", "ns2.pch.net.", "anyns.pch.net.", "ns3.pch.net."], "server": "e.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "ns3.pch.net.", "authority": ["pch.net.", "ns2.pch.net.", "anyns.pch.net.", "ns3.pch.net."], "server": "k.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "ns3.pch.net.", "authority": ["pch.net.", "ns2.pch.net.", "anyns.pch.net.", "ns3.pch.net."], "server": "i.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "ns3.pch.net.", "authority": ["pch.net.", "ns2.pch.net.", "anyns.pch.net.", "ns3.pch.net."], "server": "b.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "ns3.pch.net.", "authority": ["pch.net.", "ns2.pch.net.", "anyns.pch.net.", "ns3.pch.net."], "server": "c.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "ns3.pch.net.", "authority": ["pch.net.", "anyns.pch.net."], "server": "ns2.pch.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "ns3.pch.net.", "authority": ["pch.net.", "anyns.pch.net."], "server": "anyns.pch.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "ns3.pch.net.", "authority": ["pch.net.", "anyns.pch.net."], "server": "ns3.pch.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av1.nstld.com.", "authority": ["com.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "a.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av1.nstld.com.", "authority": ["com.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "b.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av1.nstld.com.", "authority": ["com.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "c.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av1.nstld.com.", "authority": ["com.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "d.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av1.nstld.com.", "authority": ["com.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "e.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av1.nstld.com.", "authority": ["com.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "f.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av1.nstld.com.", "authority": ["com.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "g.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av1.nstld.com.", "authority": ["com.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "h.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av1.nstld.com.", "authority": ["com.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "i.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av1.nstld.com.", "authority": ["com.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "j.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av1.nstld.com.", "authority": ["com.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "k.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av1.nstld.com.", "authority": ["com.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "l.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av1.nstld.com.", "authority": ["com.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "m.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av1.nstld.com.", "authority": ["nstld.com.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "e.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av1.nstld.com.", "authority": ["nstld.com.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "f.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av1.nstld.com.", "authority": ["nstld.com.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "i.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av1.nstld.com.", "authority": ["nstld.com.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "a.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av1.nstld.com.", "authority": ["nstld.com.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "d.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av1.nstld.com.", "authority": ["nstld.com.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "c.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av1.nstld.com.", "authority": ["nstld.com.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "m.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av1.nstld.com.", "authority": ["nstld.com.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "h.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av1.nstld.com.", "authority": ["nstld.com.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "j.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av1.nstld.com.", "authority": ["nstld.com.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "b.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av1.nstld.com.", "authority": ["nstld.com.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "g.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av1.nstld.com.", "authority": ["nstld.com.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "l.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "av1.nstld.com.", "authority": ["nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "av1.nstld.com."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "av1.nstld.com.", "authority": ["nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "av2.nstld.com."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "av1.nstld.com.", "authority": ["nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "av3.nstld.com."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "av1.nstld.com.", "authority": ["nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "av4.nstld.com."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av2.nstld.com.", "authority": ["com.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "a.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av2.nstld.com.", "authority": ["com.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "b.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av2.nstld.com.", "authority": ["com.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "c.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av2.nstld.com.", "authority": ["com.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "d.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av2.nstld.com.", "authority": ["com.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "e.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av2.nstld.com.", "authority": ["com.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "f.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av2.nstld.com.", "authority": ["com.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "g.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av2.nstld.com.", "authority": ["com.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "h.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av2.nstld.com.", "authority": ["com.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "i.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av2.nstld.com.", "authority": ["com.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "j.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av2.nstld.com.", "authority": ["com.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "k.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av2.nstld.com.", "authority": ["com.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "l.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av2.nstld.com.", "authority": ["com.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "m.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av2.nstld.com.", "authority": ["nstld.com.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "l.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av2.nstld.com.", "authority": ["nstld.com.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "c.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av2.nstld.com.", "authority": ["nstld.com.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "f.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av2.nstld.com.", "authority": ["nstld.com.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "i.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av2.nstld.com.", "authority": ["nstld.com.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "e.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av2.nstld.com.", "authority": ["nstld.com.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "g.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av2.nstld.com.", "authority": ["nstld.com.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "j.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av2.nstld.com.", "authority": ["nstld.com.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "m.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av2.nstld.com.", "authority": ["nstld.com.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "k.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av2.nstld.com.", "authority": ["nstld.com.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "b.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av2.nstld.com.", "authority": ["nstld.com.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "d.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av2.nstld.com.", "authority": ["nstld.com.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "a.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av2.nstld.com.", "authority": ["nstld.com.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "h.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "av2.nstld.com.", "authority": ["nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "av1.nstld.com."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "av2.nstld.com.", "authority": ["nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "av2.nstld.com."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "av2.nstld.com.", "authority": ["nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "av3.nstld.com."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "av2.nstld.com.", "authority": ["nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "av4.nstld.com."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av3.nstld.com.", "authority": ["com.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "a.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av3.nstld.com.", "authority": ["com.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "b.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av3.nstld.com.", "authority": ["com.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "c.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av3.nstld.com.", "authority": ["com.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "d.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av3.nstld.com.", "authority": ["com.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "e.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av3.nstld.com.", "authority": ["com.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "f.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av3.nstld.com.", "authority": ["com.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "g.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av3.nstld.com.", "authority": ["com.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "h.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av3.nstld.com.", "authority": ["com.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "i.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av3.nstld.com.", "authority": ["com.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "j.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av3.nstld.com.", "authority": ["com.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "k.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av3.nstld.com.", "authority": ["com.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "l.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av3.nstld.com.", "authority": ["com.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "m.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av3.nstld.com.", "authority": ["nstld.com.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "f.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av3.nstld.com.", "authority": ["nstld.com.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "h.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av3.nstld.com.", "authority": ["nstld.com.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "j.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av3.nstld.com.", "authority": ["nstld.com.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "e.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av3.nstld.com.", "authority": ["nstld.com.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "k.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av3.nstld.com.", "authority": ["nstld.com.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "d.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av3.nstld.com.", "authority": ["nstld.com.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "g.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av3.nstld.com.", "authority": ["nstld.com.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "m.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av3.nstld.com.", "authority": ["nstld.com.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "i.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av3.nstld.com.", "authority": ["nstld.com.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "l.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av3.nstld.com.", "authority": ["nstld.com.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "a.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av3.nstld.com.", "authority": ["nstld.com.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "c.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av3.nstld.com.", "authority": ["nstld.com.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "b.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "av3.nstld.com.", "authority": ["nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "av1.nstld.com."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "av3.nstld.com.", "authority": ["nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "av2.nstld.com."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "av3.nstld.com.", "authority": ["nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "av3.nstld.com."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "av3.nstld.com.", "authority": ["nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "av4.nstld.com."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av4.nstld.com.", "authority": ["com.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "a.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av4.nstld.com.", "authority": ["com.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "b.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av4.nstld.com.", "authority": ["com.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "c.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av4.nstld.com.", "authority": ["com.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "d.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av4.nstld.com.", "authority": ["com.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "e.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av4.nstld.com.", "authority": ["com.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "f.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av4.nstld.com.", "authority": ["com.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "g.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av4.nstld.com.", "authority": ["com.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "h.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av4.nstld.com.", "authority": ["com.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "i.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av4.nstld.com.", "authority": ["com.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "j.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av4.nstld.com.", "authority": ["com.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "k.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av4.nstld.com.", "authority": ["com.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "l.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av4.nstld.com.", "authority": ["com.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net."], "server": "m.root-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av4.nstld.com.", "authority": ["nstld.com.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "m.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av4.nstld.com.", "authority": ["nstld.com.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "d.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av4.nstld.com.", "authority": ["nstld.com.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "e.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av4.nstld.com.", "authority": ["nstld.com.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "i.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av4.nstld.com.", "authority": ["nstld.com.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "k.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av4.nstld.com.", "authority": ["nstld.com.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "b.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av4.nstld.com.", "authority": ["nstld.com.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "c.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av4.nstld.com.", "authority": ["nstld.com.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "h.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av4.nstld.com.", "authority": ["nstld.com.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "a.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av4.nstld.com.", "authority": ["nstld.com.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "l.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av4.nstld.com.", "authority": ["nstld.com.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "j.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av4.nstld.com.", "authority": ["nstld.com.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "f.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av4.nstld.com.", "authority": ["nstld.com.", "av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "g.gtld-servers.net."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "av4.nstld.com.", "authority": ["nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "av1.nstld.com."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "av4.nstld.com.", "authority": ["nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "av2.nstld.com."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "av4.nstld.com.", "authority": ["nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "av3.nstld.com."}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "av4.nstld.com.", "authority": ["nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."], "server": "av4.nstld.com."}]